<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoviTrack</string>

    <string name="active">Active</string>
    <string name="recovered">Recovered</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="deaths">Deaths</string>
    <string name="covid_19">Covid-19</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="cases">Cases</string>
    <string name="increment_number">+232325</string>
    <string name="number">2323236544</string>

    <string name="findHead"><br>How to Find the MAC Address of Your Device</br></string>

    <string name="findPara"><br>1. On your Home screen press the Menu button and Settings.</br>\n\n<br>2. Scroll down to About Device and press Status.</br>\n\n<br>3. Scroll down till you find the Wi-Fi MAC address entry.</br>\n\n<br>4. This is you devices MAC address.</br>\n\n<br>5. Directly below that is your Bluetooth MAC address.</br></string>

    <string name="positivePara"><br>\u2022 If you have an emergency warning sign (trouble breathing), seek emergency medical care immediately.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Stay in a separate room from other household members, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Use a separate bathroom, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Take steps to improve ventilation at home, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Avoid contact with other members of the household and pets.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Don’t share personal household items, like cups, towels, and utensils.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Wear a well-fitting mask when you need to be around other people.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Once you isolate for at least 5 days, if you are fever free and your other symptoms have improved, you can end isolation</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Use an antigen test towards the end of the 5-day isolation period. If your test result is positive, you should continue to isolate until day 10. If your test result is negative, you can end isolation</br></string>

    <string name="highRiskPara"><br>\u2022 Seek emergency medical care immediately.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Stay in a separate room from other household members, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Use a separate bathroom, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Take steps to improve ventilation at home, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Avoid contact with other members of the household and pets.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Don’t share personal household items, like cups, towels, and utensils.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Wear a well-fitting mask when you need to be around other people.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Once you isolate for at least 10 days, if you are fever free and your other symptoms have improved, you can end isolation</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Use an antigen test towards the end of the 10-day isolation period. If your test result is positive, you should continue to isolate until day 20. If your test result is negative, you can end isolation</br></string>

    <string name="moderateRiskPara"><br>\u2022 Stay in a separate room from other household members, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Use a separate bathroom, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Take steps to improve ventilation at home, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Avoid contact with other members of the household and pets.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Don’t share personal household items, like cups, towels, and utensils.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Wear a well-fitting mask when you need to be around other people.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Once you isolate for at least 10 days, if you are fever free and your other symptoms have improved, you can end isolation</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 If you are unsure if your symptoms are moderate, talk to a healthcare provider for further guidance.</br></string>

    <string name="closeContactPara"><br>\u2022 Stay home and away from other people for at least 5 days.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Wear a well-fitting mask when around others at home, if possible.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 For 10 days, watch for fever (100.4◦F or greater), cough, shortness of breath, or other COVID-19 symptoms.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 If you develop symptoms, get tested immediately and isolate until you receive your test results. If you test positive, follow isolation recommendations.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 If you do not develop symptoms, get tested at least after 5 days.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 If possible, stay away from people you live with, especially people who are at higher risk for getting very sick from COVID-19, as well as others outside your home throughout the full 10 days.</br>\n\n<br>\u2022 Do not go to places where you are unable to wear a mask, such as restaurants and some gyms, and avoid eating around others at home and at work for 10 days.</br>\n\n</string>

    <string-array name="fever" colors="block">
        <item>No</item>
        <item>1-5 Days</item>
        <item>5-10 Days</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="test">
        <item>Not done</item>
        <item>Negative</item>
        <item>Positive</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>